A Preliminary Inventory of the Deaver & Hannaford, Inc. Records, 1960-2008
Hoover Institution Archives
- Campaign, 1976
  - July
    - 17-25 (Folder 54: 4)
    - 26-31 (Folder 54: 5)
  - August
    - 1-7 (Folder 54: 6)
    - 8-15 (Folder 54: 7)
    - 16-18 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - 19-31 (Folder 55: 2)
  - September 1-30 (Folder 55: 3-4)
  - October 1-31 (Folder 55: 5)
  - November (Folder 55: 6)
    (Ronald Reagan)
  - December (Folder 55: 7)
- Reports, State of California, 1968-1973 (Box 56)
  - General, 1976 and undated (Folder 56: 1)
  - 1968-1973 (Folder 56: 2-3)
- Speeches by Governor Ronald Reagan, 1974
  - Interview, Meet the Press, James J. Kilpatrick, Washington Star Syndicate; Tom Braden, Los Angeles Times Syndicate; Robert Novak, Chicago Sun-Times; and Catherine Mackin, NBC News as panelists, 1974 January 20. (Folder 56: 4)
    Printed copy
  - Commencement Address, California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, 1974 June 15.
- Study, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 57: 1-4)
- Clippings and printed matter, 1976 (Box-folder 58: 1-3)
- "Summary of Actions and Programs of Governor Ronald Reagan's Administration, 1967-1974.", See also box 65 (Box 59)
  - 1974 December (Folder 59: 1-4)
  - 1974 December (Box-folder 60: 1-5)
- Governor Ronald Reagan, 1975-1979. (Box 61)
  Includes Nancy Reagan
  - Clippings and news summary, 1975 (Folder 61: 1-3)
  - Schedules, 1979 (Folder 61: 4)
- Clippings and printed matter, 1975-1976. (Box 62)
  Includes news summary
  - 1975 (Folder 62: 1-5)
  - 1976 (Box 63)
    - January (Folder 63: 1)
    - February (Folder 63: 2)
    - March
      - 1-15 (Folder 63: 3)
      - 17-30 (Folder 63: 4)
    - April
      - 1-22 (Folder 63: 5)
      - 23-30 (Folder 63: 6)
    - May (Box 64)
      - 1-13 (Folder 64: 1)
      - 14-25 (Folder 64: 2)
    - August 6-30 (Folder 64: 3)
    - September 3-28 (Folder 64: 4)
    - October 1-29 (Folder 64: 5)
    - November 1-30 (Folder 64: 6)
    - December 1-29 (Folder 64: 7)
- "Revenue Control and Tax Deduction,", 1973 March 12 (Box-folder 65: 1-2)
- "California's Experience with Welfare Reform,", 1974 December (Folder 65: 3)
- "Summary of Actions and Programs of Governor Ronald Reagan's Administration, 1967-1974,", 1974 December.; See also boxes 59 and 60 (Folder 65: 4-5)
- "California Tax Limitation Plan," study, 1973 May (Box-folder 66: 1)
- "California State-Wide Tax Limitation Initiative," survey, 1973 August.; See also boxes 75 and 77 (Folder 66: 2)
- "Tax Limitation Plan,", 1973 October.; See also boxes 74 and 76 (Box-folder 67: 1)
- "Tax Limitation Initiative: Post Election Study,", 1973 November (Folder 67: 2)
- "California Health Security Program, " undated; "Six Basic Plan Concepts Used for California School Housing," undated; "Stock Plans for Schools," 1969; "The People's Park: A Report on a Confrontation at Berkeley, California," 1969 July 1; "Time Is Running Out, The Environmental Crisis: A Call to Action," summary proceedings, Governor's Conference on California's Changing Environment, Los Angeles, California, 1969 November 17-18; Pacific Business, 1970 January-February; Careers in California State Government, 1971.; See also box 70 (Box-folder 68: 1)
- California Health Security Program, undated; Inaugural Message of Ronald Reagan, 1967 January 5; Budget Message of Ronald Reagan, 1967-1971; Text of State of the State message, 1968-1970; State of California Budget Summary, 1970-1971; and Inaugural address of Governor Ronald Reagan, 1971 January 4 (Folder 68: 2)
- Reports: "Emission Inventories," 1969 November; "Air Pollution Control in California," 1970 January; and State of California: Environmental Quality Study Council,", 1970-1971 (Folder 68: 3)
- Report of the Governor's Commission on the Law of Preemption, undated; "Violence in the City: An End or a Beginning?" Report by the Governor's Commission on Los Angeles Riots, 1965 December 2; Tax Message of Ronald Reagan, Governor of California, 1967 March 8; Tax Reform Program for California, 1969 April; "Budget Message," 1969-1973; Report to Governor Ronald Reagan on Violence in California Prisons, 1971 October 7 (Folder 68: 4)
- Economic report of the Governor, 1967-1973; reorganization of the executive branch of the California state government, 1969-1971; health reorganization message, 1970; "Is the Present Anxiety About Public Education Justified?" remarks, Alex C. Sherriffs, Rational Debate Seminar, American Enterprise Institute, Washington, D.C., 1970 May 6; and "Public Challenge and Campus Response," Alex C. Sheriffs, Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, University of California, Berkeley, 1971 July 12 (Box-folder 69: 1)
- "Reorganization Message of Ronald Reagan: Governor of California," 1969 March 5 and "Progress Report on Development of State Environmental Goals and Policy,", 1971 June 1.; See also box 70 (Folder 69: 2)
- Remarks by Governor Ronald Reagan, 1971-1972
  - State of the State Message, 1971 January 12, typescript; Commonwealth Club of California, 1971 June 22, typescript; Republican State Central Committee Meeting, Los Angeles, California, 1971 October 2, typescript; and Long Beach Joint Service Clubs, Long Beach, California, 1972 April 7, typescript (Folder 69: 3)
- Writings by others about Governor Ronald Reagan's records and policies, 1967-1974
  - "The Equal Education Plan for Higher Education in California," 1967 July 25; "California Quenches Her Big Thirst," James H. Winchester, Reader's Digest, 1970; and "Governor Ronald Reagan: Action and Result,", 1974 February (Folder 69: 4)
- Law and order, 1972 and undated
  - Crime, undated (Folder 69: 5)
  - Drugs, 1972 (Folder 69: 6)
  - Environment, 1972 (Folder 69: 7)
- Budget message of Governor Ronald Reagan, 1969 February 4 (Box-folder 70: 1)
- Creative papers, undated (Folder 70: 2)
- Education, 1970-1972 (Folder 70: 3)
- Environmental goals and policies, 1972 March 1.; See also box 69 (Folder 70: 4)
- "Higher Education," report, Ronald Reagan, 1968 December 8 (Folder 70: 5)
- Reagan--General issues, 1969-1971. (Folder 70: 6)
  Includes some of Governor Reagan's speeches. Printed copy
- "Time Is Running Out," excerpts of remarks, Governor Ronald Reagan, Governor's Environmental Conference, Los Angeles, California, 1969 November 18; and "Our Nation Is Founded...Colleges,", undated (Folder 70: 7)
  See also box 68
- "Revenue Control and Tax Reduction," report submitted by Governor Ronald Reagan to the California Legislature, 1973 March 12 (Box-folder 71: 1-4)
- Speeches, 1978 (Box 72)
  - "How They Stand: Presidential Candidates' Positions,", 1969-1976 (Folder 72: 1)
  - "Where Reagan Stands," interview on the issues, U.S. News & World Report, 1976 May 31 (Folder 72: 2)
  - "How Reagan Will Win," interview, John Sears, New Guard, 1976 August (Folder 72: 3)
- "Nielson DMA Secondary Markets by Regions," report, undated (Box-folder 73: 1)
- "Nielson DMA Top 50: Market Rankings," report, undated (Folder 73: 2)
- "Tax Limitation Plan,", 1973 June. (Box-folder 74: 1)
  See also box 67 and 76
- "Tax Limitation Initiative Survey,", 1973 August.; See also boxes 66 and 77 (Box-folder 75: 1)
- "Tax Limitation Plan,", 1973 July.; See also boxes 67 and 74 (Box-folder 76: 1)
- "Tax Limitation Initiative Survey,", 1973 August.; See also boxes 66 and 75 (Box-folder 77: 1)
- Newspaper clippings, 1978 (Box-folder 78: 1-3)
- Newspaper clippings, 1978 (Box-folder 79: 1-2)
- Ronald Reagan (Box 80)
  - News summaries
    - 1975
      - January - May (Folder 80: 1-4)
      - June - September (Box-folder 81: 1-4)
      - October – November (Box-folder 82: 1-2)
    - 1977
      - January - February (Folder 82: 3-4)
      - March – July (Box-folder 83: 1-5)
      - August - December (Box-folder 84: 1-5)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 85: 1-3)
      - January - April
  - Clippings (Box 86)
    - 1975 November (Folder 86: 1)
    - 1978
      - March - May 3 (Folder 86: 2-9)
      - May 4-31 (Box-folder 87: 1-6)
      - May 1-31 (Box-folder 88: 1-5)
      - June (Box-folder 89: 1)
      - June 1-15 (Folder 89: 2-6)
      - June 16-30 (Box-folder 90: 1-5)
      - July 1-31 (Box-folder 91: 1-6)
- Deaver & Hannaford press clippings, 1978 (Box 92)
  - June 23 - August 7 (Folder 92: 1-7)
  - August 1-15 (Box-folder 93: 1-8)
  - August 16-30 (Box-folder 94: 1-6)
  - September 1-15 (Box-folder 95: 1-6)
  - September 16-30 (Box-folder 96: 1-2)
  - October (Folder 96: 3)
- California Journal, 1970-1980 (Folder 96: 4)
- Card file (Box 97)
- Incremental Materials (Box 98-100)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described. Contact us at hooverarchivesinfo@stanford.edu